Yeah, yeah, yeah.
This story is best told
from the beginning.
It was 1965, and a storm
raged both outside and within.
Prisoner 696, what's going on back there?
Hey, what's the problem, 696?
Didn't end up agreeing with you.
Girlie's pregnant?
We're a remote women's prison.
Our security is top-notch.
No guy could get in.
Also, when did it happen?
She's here for eight years
for robbery and assault.
And she's two wins, so this
doesn't make any sense.
Neither of you know when this happened.
There wasn't so much as
a bump this afternoon.
It's crazy.
Time to talk, Chaka.
Who's the kid's daddy?
You didn't knock up yourself.
The father is dead already.
Over two years ago.
Huh?
Yeah, that's a good one.
I got some I want to
share with you too, lady.
It's all the barnacles grown in my knee.
Want to see them?
Looks like the kid made it.
Yeah, but he's a strange one.
This little rugrat was born
with his eyes wide open.
But the really bizarre thing
is, he hasn't cried at all.
Look, I don't have to tell you,
this is no place for a baby.
He'll have to be adopted.
So, where are you from, anyway?
Sardinia.
In time, the child was taken in
by a village priest on the island.
Time seemed to fly by,
and over the years, the young boy gained
a reputation for his bashful naivete.
Well, I better get going.
See you later, Mr.
Froggy.
Watch where you're going, you brat!
Oh, it's just you again!
Out of the road, Katsune!
And don't blabber to Padre!
Geez, they were mean.
But still, I'm glad you're
okay, my little amiko.
You like frogs, huh?
I do too.
But I can't stand bugs.
I'm not too fond of
funky-smelling guys either.
I hate anything that isn't beautiful.
You from around here or what?
Uh, yeah, I guess I am.
Hey, uh, would you like
something cold to drink?
Hmm, well, I...
Guess it couldn't hurt.
So how does sparkling water sound?
You know, French mineral water.
Your treat, okay?
You want to become a sailor? I do.
That's excellent.
Especially for a simple
soul like yours. Yes.
I believe you'll make a wonderful mariner.
What's this?
The fact that he walked all
the way here is impressive.
Good on the lad.
I suppose it's time he had a car.
Wanting to build a carport
next to the boy's room,
the priest began digging up the
floor tiles and underlying concrete.
Who?
What in the...
A corpse?
No.
He carefully chiseled away at the floor,
until he uncovered her?
the woman who gave birth
to his adopted son.
Sh-she's alive.
She was paralyzed and unable to speak.
But something was keeping her
tethered to the world of the living.
She lay buried for years.
Her mind vacant with
no conception of time.
Whether by hatred or love.
Her heart had been obfuscated by darkness.
The hair is the same color as.
That night, a horrific
fire ravaged the village,
strengthened by the night's howling winds.
While no cause could be found, Seven died,
while countless others remained missing.
Among those listed on the
coroner's report were the
village priest and the adopted
son he loved so dearly.
Why you...
Hey, look out!
What are you doing?!
Oh, shut up. I'm not dumb.
There's a truck bearing down, right?
Hey!
Go take your Sunday stroll somewhere
else, you freakin' Straizo!
Ow.
Man, that hurt.
Guess I was wrong.
Doesn't seem to be your day, huh, kiddo?
Or am I sensing more of a
rough patch in your life?
You're one hell of a psychic, because
I've got nothing but problems.
Would you be interested
in hearing your fortune?
It comes at a special rate.
huh thanks but no sardinia
is the locale of your birth
isn't that correct not only
the hat but you haven't
been back to the old stomping
grounds in quite some
time that's not exactly
fortune-telling of course
you can tell I'm visiting
from out of town my outfit
is a total giveaway dear
ragazzo you harbor a great
secret within you a shadow
in the Sun two sides of
a coin you child lead two entirely
dissimilar lives. Moreover,
you take advantage of
your harrowing secret,
which combined with your
tenacious personality?
has earned you a great many victories.
What did you say?
Ah, scusi, I spoke out of turn.
Please understand, your face is very
beguiling to a fortune teller like myself.
Allow me the honor of
telling your fortune.
Twenty, no, ten thousand lira will do.
Come, sir.
Who among us doesn't have
one secret or another?
All of this stuff could apply to anyone.
You're searching for somebody.
Interesting.
This person is very important to you.
That is so true.
Aren't all of us just looking for
someone who's important to us?
We're desperate for the perfect
partner or faultless friend.
You know, it's kind of fun
having someone guess your future.
How do you do that anyway?
With that crystal ball?
No.
I've already begun by other means.
For example, the mud on your
trousers tells me a great deal. Huh?
The Romani have practiced
this divination for millennia.
The spontaneity of nature holds powers
greater than our wildest imaginations.
That splatter is a symbol of
mankind's fate. Your daughter.
Yes, the person who you've come all
this way to find is your daughter.
You've returned to Sardinia
to find the child you
fathered with the woman you
left behind 15 years ago huh?
How very strange your youthfulness
I know I just uttered those
words but I'm completely baffled
you think I'm a father yes?
Really I'm quite certain of it I must
read your palm hey I beg of you my worth
as a fortune teller hinges on this I
don't want your money in fact I'll pay 20,
100,000 Lira!
I'm bleeding here!
Leave me the hell alone!
Don't you dare touch me!
So what if you could predict the future?
That ability will be useless
to you once you're dead!
What's this?
Your face?
Seems you're not a stand user.
Pity you've had to peddle
your talents of perception
on the side of the road
like a common beggar.
It was the greatest misstep of your life.
You see, Divine,
anyone who possesses any knowledge of my
true self must not be allowed to live.
But you have proven yourself to be a
fortune teller of the highest caliber.
You've my admiration,
so I shall kill you in a way that
inflicts the least amount of pain.
But my generosity comes with a price.
The traitor in this picture
is known as Risotto.
He desires to reveal my true identity,
and has made it his mission
to seek out my daughter.
Use your divination to
reveal this man's location.
You want his location?
I'm sorry, but I can't say.
Though I'm sure you'll
encounter him soon enough.
He has come to Sardinia.
His heart burns with revenge.
There's no question your paths will cross.
I see. Understood.
That will suffice.
I knew it!
I knew I was right about your nature.
It's truly like two sides of a coin.
You're a dual personality.
As long as you bear this secret,
the death of others
will be your fortune and
eternal glory will spring
forth from your fingertips.
Oh, your glorious palm
glows with stunning beauty.
Never have I seen a hand so handsome.
What happened?
Everything looks different.
This isn't how the lifeline was at all.
Now I get it.
I'm holding my own severed hand.
How did that happen?
Emperor Crimson.
You there!
I'm glad you weren't flattened.
This is no place for a guy like you.
Go on now, get out of here.
Be careful out there, okay?
Where to, signore?
Costa Smeralda, please. Cierto.
Our next story comes to us from Sardinia,
where the investigation of an airplane
crash near the city of Olvia continues.
Despite a strong effort...
Scusi, would you happen to
have a phone I could use?
Mine's totally broken.
Sorry, but I don't, kid.
Oh.
Stop!
Driver, stop the taxi!
I need to get out, and here
is as good a spot as any.
That's the building.
I know it.
All I have to do is keep
an eye on that spot.
The Costa Smeralda of Sardinia.
Just over a half a century ago,
before the beauty of its waters and shore
caught the eyes of an Indian magnet,
the secluded locale was practically
unknown to the outside world.
Wait a sec.
I think your meter may be off by a digit.
Oh, I see how it is.
You're accusing me of ripping
you off by rigging the meter.
Is that what you're saying, huh?
No, but 800,000 lira to go from
town to here seems a bit much.
I don't have it.
Like someone coming
here doesn't have cash.
Don't think I didn't see you hiding
something when you were back there.
In fact, I saw you stashing
an envelope in your pants.
Don't!
You can't trick me.
Don't touch me.
My head!
You see? Bingo!
How dare you!
You should have kept
those peepers to yourself.
Your damn curiosity's
about to get you killed!
You're insane!
Do-do-do. Ugh.
Wait, hang on.
Did you hear that just now? Huh?
The phone rang.
Hey, answer the damn question!
No way that busted up phone
was ringing, so what gives?
I, I don't know, what you're even taught.
Do-do-do-do-do.
Huh? There it is again. Where is it?
Where is it?
Do-do-do-do.
So you do have a working phone!
You've been holding out on me, Mr.
Driver!
Hello?
Yes, it's Deep.
Boss, yes, I just arrived.
Same spot as the photo.
So all I've got to do is
keep an eye out, right?
Huh?
So because he didn't get a good look at
what was inside, he's allowed to live?
What?
Not to question your
infinite wisdom, boss,
but I'm pretty positive the driver
saw something he shouldn't have seen.
Yes, my apologies, boss.
I've already begun keeping
watch over the building.
You think you're watching the building?
I'd re-evaluate, Deep.
Look harder, but move slow.
Make no sudden movements.
You must not appear flustered.
The one who's being watched
right now is you, Deep.
What?
That's Risotto!
He's one of the traitors
from the Hitman team!
That Ian Dolphin was right! There he is!
He's certainly a crafty one.
The plane crash managed to tip him off to
the photo of Sardinia from Trisha's house.
Our first order of business
is to take him out.
Otherwise, he'll be even more
trouble once Trisha arrives.
Just leave the killing blow to me.
I'll handle it.
Your job is to close the distance between
us without revealing your true identity.
Even I have no insight
into Risotto's abilities.
Lure him within two meters of us.
I need the fool well within
Emperor Crimson's range.
So I'll leave it to you.
Ciao, Doppio.
Atta, mi caro. Right.
You can count on me, boss.
What's going on here?
My head is killing me!
Oh yeah, that's the least of my worries.
The boss just called with a direct order.
I have to keep an eye on the
building, and then I need to...
To...
What did he say? Close the gap?
That's right. Move in closer.
Okay, but closer to what?
It won't happen, so don't stress.
Over here.
What the...
I know I've seen that face before.
But who is he?
Move your hand away.
I want to see your face.
Please, sir, I don't have any money.
It's my blood.
Oh, man.
Why does this always have to happen to me?
Guess I was wrong.
This coward doesn't have the
faintest clue what's going on.
He's pathetic.
No one from Passione
would behave like this.
Besides, he's practically
begging to be attacked.
Looks like he's just your
run-of-the-mill brat.
Please, don't!
Give it a rest.
I'm just grabbing my knife.
You're of no interest to me now.
I don't feel so good.
My head is aching.
Two meters.
That's right.
And now that I'm remembering, you did
do something kind of fishy back there.
When you tripped and fell on your face,
you almost reflexively hid
the envelope on the ground.
I'm pretty sure I saw you hide it.
Under your foot. So what's inside?
If it's nothing, I'll be on my way.
What do you want?
Look, I told you I'm broke!
Just let me go in peace!
I sense no bloodlust or hostility.
But still, I know a liar when I see one.
Stand up and show me what
you're hiding underfoot.
I set up, dammit! Hop-to!
Oh, shit.
It is just an envelope.
The thing's totally empty.
Guess the groveling
wasn't an act after all.
You're just a coward who
can't lie to save his life.
That said, everything's changed.
You intrigue me more
and more every second.
I have no doubt you're a stand user.
You also heard that sound, didn't you?
Just now, you made a stealthy
glance towards that whirring noise.
Someone's combing the place.
They're carrying out a
reconnaissance mission.
That could only be one stand!
Will Bomber!
They finally made it to Sardinia!
Well now, you'd have to be very
special to be sent to this location.
Clearly the boss has a
tremendous deal of faith in you.
Despite all that, your
fear's 100 % genuine.
You are quite the
fascinating contradiction!
Stop talking!
The only one who's going to be
quaking with fear is you, Stronezo!
Interesting.
Your charging ahead tells me you're
a close-range user with power.
Your range is two or three
meters, as long as I know that.
Killing you's easy. What?
My throat!
What the hell is this?
These actual razor blades!
I just need to get within two
meters of this edgy douche!
Once I do, I'll jam these
blades straight up his ass!
Like I said, I know just how to kill you.
Damn that hurt, but you're still dead!
He's gone?
That must be it.
That's his special ability.
But how am I supposed to...
I know I heard a phone ringing.
That's incredible.
Who would ever guess there'd be
a payphone all the way out here?
Hello?
My Deep.
Where are you, boss?
Are you here?
Are you nearby?
I need your help with this.
No, the time is not yet right.
Until you close the gap between
the two of you, I cannot act.
If he catches sight of me
and manages to get away,
all our efforts will have been for naught.
But boss...
You know what to do.
Move within two meters of risotto.
Boss, I still have no
idea how his powers work.
He's just gonna get me again.
Oh, Deep.
Dear Deep.
My sweet, charming Deep.
Have you so easily
forgotten that I bestowed
you with part of Emperor Crimson's power?
Now's your chance to
apply your unique talents.
Is just fiction.
Or what is the truth?
They have a mission.
They are a blessing.
They dare to tell us.
What's bad and what's good.
Stand up!
Join us!
Come on!
Just say this.
We are the power!
Who's in the future?
This is we are. The fighters.
Just fighting for. The rise.
Alright.
Thank you.